midlifeattheoasis.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy

                                      Privacy Policy
Midlife At The Oasis understands the importance of your personal privacy. Therefore, we have
created this Privacy Policy so that you know how we use and disclose your information when
you make it available to us. The Privacy Policy below discloses our practices regarding
information collection and usage website located at ​http://midlifeattheoasis.com​, the related
mobile website, and the service provided thereon (the “Service”).
By using or accessing the Websites and the Service, you signify your agreement to be bound by
this Privacy Policy. ​IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT
ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE OUR SERVICE OR PARTICIPATE IN OUR SERVICES​. Key
aspects of our privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy include the following
explanations:
• The information we collect and why we collect it;
• How we use that information;
• How we share information; and
• The choices we offer. Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect: We may ask you for,
or you may voluntarily submit, personally identifiable information when you are using the
Service. The personally identifiable information which you may provide to us could include, but
is not limited to: · Your name · Your contact information (including, without limitation, address
and email address); · Your IP address; and · Other personal information. Non-Personal Or
Aggregate Information That We Collect: When you access our Service, we may automatically
collect non-personally identifiable information from you, such as IP host address, web pages
viewed, browser type, operating system, referring service, search information, device type, page
views, usage and browsing habits on the Service and similar data. We may also aggregate
demographic information collected from our users (such as the number of users in a particular
geographical location) in a manner which does not identify any one individual. We may also
aggregate information collected offline in connection with the Service, obtain non-personally
identifiable information from third party sources and develop aggregate information by
anonymizing previously collected personally identifiable information. It is possible at times when
collecting non-personally identifiable information through automatic means that we may
unintentionally collect or receive personally identifiable information that is mixed in with the
non-personally identifiable information. While we will make reasonable efforts to prevent such
incidental data collection, the possibility still exists. If you believe that we have inadvertently
collected your personal information, please notify us at ​Lois@themidlifeoasis.com​.

Information Usage: We will only use your personally identifiable information as described below,
unless you have specifically consented to another type of use, either at the time the personally
identifiable information is collected from you or through some other form of consent from you or
notification to you: ·We may share your personally identifiable information collected in
connection with providing the Service. ·We may use your personally identifiable information to
respond to your inquiries or requests. ·We may use your personally identifiable information to
send you emails from time to time about our services, but we will not provide your personally
identifiable information to third parties for them to contact you directly unless otherwise
permitted by this Privacy Policy or you provide your consent. ·
We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties (collectively, the “Third
Party Vendors”) to further the purpose for which you provided such information to us. For
example, we may share your information with Elastic Email, for the purpose of sending emails.
We urge you to read the privacy practices of all of our Third-Party Vendors before submitting
any personally identifiable information through the Service. ·
We may disclose personally identifiable information as required by law or legal process. ·We
may disclose personally identifiable information to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or
other violations of any law, rule or regulation, or the terms or policies for our services or our
sponsors. ·We may transfer your personally identifiable information in connection with the sale
or merger or change of control of MIDLIFE AT THE OASIS or the division responsible for the
services with which your personally identifiable information is associated. ·We may share your
personally identifiable information with an affiliate of MIDLIFE AT THE OASIS who is in the
same corporate family as us as long as their privacy practices are substantially similar to ours.
Non-personally identifiable or aggregate information may be used by us for any purposes
permitted by law and may be shared with any number of parties, provided that such information
shall not specifically identify you. Cookies and Similar Technologies: “Cookies” are pieces of
information that may be placed on your computer by a service for the purpose of facilitating and
enhancing your communication and interaction with that service. Many services use cookies for
these purposes. We may use cookies (and similar items such as clear gifs, web beacons, tags,
etc.) on our Service to customize your visit and for other purposes to make your visit more
convenient or to enable us to enhance our Service. We may also use and place cookies (and
similar items) on your computer from our third-party service providers in connection with the
Service, such as an analytics provider that helps us manage and analyze Service usage, as
described more fully below.
In addition, our advertisers and business partners may set cookies and similar items on your
computer when you use our Service. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your
computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which
case you may still use our Service, but it may interfere with some of its functionality. Cookies
and similar items are not used by us to automatically retrieve personally identifiable information
from your computer without your knowledge. If you delete your cookies, change browsers or use

a different cookie, our cookie (or an opt-out cookie) may no longer work and you will have to
re-input (or opt-out) again.
Analytics and Conversion Tracking: We may use analytics services that use cookies, javascript
and similar technologies to help us analyze how users use the Service. The information
generated by these services about your use of the Service (including your IP address or a
truncated version of your IP address) is transmitted to and stored by analytics service providers
on their servers. Those service providers will use this information for the purpose of evaluating
your, and other users’, use of the Service, compiling reports for us on website activity and
providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. We may collect
information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser
type, for system administration and in order to create reports. This is statistical data about our
users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. For example, we use
cookies on our site for Google Analytics (the “Analytics Service”). The Analytics Service is a
web-based analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their
website. The Analytics Service customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors
interact with their website so that they can improve it. Like many services, the Analytics Service
uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions as in our case, where they are used to collect
information about how visitors use our site. We then use the information to compile reports and
to help us improve our site. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s
hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit
occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the
web page. The Analytics Service collects information anonymously. They report website trends
without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of the Analytics Service without affecting
how you visit our site.
For more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you
use, visit ​https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout​. We may also use Google conversion
tracking and/or similar services to help us understand your and other users’ use of the Service.
Automatically Collected Information: When you access the Service or open one of our HTML
emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using cookies and
other types of tracking technologies. This "automatically collected" information may include
Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), a unique user ID, device type, device identifiers,
browser types and language, referring and exit pages, platform type, version of software
installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the Service, the number of
clicks, the amount of time spent on pages, the dates and times that you visit the Service, and
other similar information.

Depending on the law of your country of residence, your IP address may legally be considered
personally identifiable information. Security: The security of your personally identifiable
information is very important to us. When we collect your personally identifiable information
online, we use reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access. However, due to the
inherent open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable
information will be completely free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers
and your use of our Service demonstrates your assumption of this risk. We have put in place
reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we
collect. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to perform their
duties are authorized to have access to your personally identifiable information.
For more information on protecting your privacy, please visit ​www.ftc.gov/privacy​. Your
Disclosures In Blogs And Other Social Media: You should be aware that personally identifiable
information which you voluntarily include and transmit online on the Service or in a publicly
accessible blog, chat room, social media platform or otherwise online, or that you share in an
open forum such as an in-person panel or survey, may be viewed and used by others without
any restrictions. We are unable to control such uses of your personally identifiable information,
and by using the Service or any other online services you assume the risk that the personally
identifiable information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties for any number
of purposes. If you login to the Websites and/or Service through your Facebook account,
connect to a third party service such as Facebook or Twitter through an icon or link on the
Service or otherwise link your MIDLIFE AT THE OASIS account with a third party service, we
may share the contents of your post and associated information (such as your user name, the
fact that your connection originated from the Service, and other relevant usage and diagnostic
information) with such third party. With your one-time consent, we may also send information
about the content you watch and your activities on the Service to such third parties. Once such
information is shared, the use of your information will be subject to that service's privacy policy
and this Privacy Policy will not apply.
Protection for Children: We generally do not collect personally identifiable information from
children under the age of 13. If at any time in the future we plan to collect personally identifiable
information from children under 13, such collection and use, to the extent applicable, shall,
when required, be done in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act
(“COPPA”) and appropriate consent from the child’s parent or guardian will be sought where
required by COPPA. When we become aware that personally identifiable information from a
child under 13 has been collected without such child’s parent or guardian’s consent, we will use
all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

Other Services: As a convenience to you, we may provide links to third-party Services from
within our Service. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these
third-party sites. When you link away from our Service, you do so at your own risk.
Changes to this Privacy Policy: We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add,
or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we
plan to use personally identifiable information in a way that materially differs from this Privacy
Policy, including sharing such information with more third parties, we will post such changes
here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the
Service and our services following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy means you
accept such changes. ​Opt-Out Process: All unsubscribe, or opt-out requests may be made
by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the relevant email​. We will process your
request within a reasonable time after receipt. However, we are not responsible for, and in some
cases we are incapable of, removing your personally identifiable information from the lists of any
third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this Privacy
Policy or your consent. You should contact such third parties directly. If you would like to update
or correct any personally identifiable information that you have provided to us, please email us
at ​Lois@midlifeattheoasis.com​ and once we confirm your information, we will update such
information within a reasonable amount of time.
Communications with MIDLIFE AT THE OASIS: By providing your contact information to us
(including, without limitation, your email address, physical address, and phone number)
(collectively the “Channels”) to us, you expressly consent to receive communications from us.
We may use the Channels to communicate with you, to send information that you have
requested or to send information about other products or services developed or provided by us
or our business partners, provided that, we will not give your contact information to another
party to promote their products or services directly to you without your consent or as set forth in
this Privacy Policy.
By using the Service, you expressly consent to receive in-product communications from us
(including, without limitation, push notifications on the App). By providing your phone number to
us, you expressly consent to receive phone calls and/or text messages from us. We will not give
your phone number to another party to promote their products or services directly to you without
your consent or as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Any phone calls and/or text messages
delivered to your phone or device may cause you to incur extra data, text messaging, or other
charges from your wireless carrier. MESSAGE AND DATA RATES MAY APPLY. You are solely
responsible for any carrier charges incurred as a result of phone and/or text communications
from MIDLIFE AT THE OASIS.

Any communication or material you transmit to us by email or otherwise, including any data,
questions, comments, suggestions, or the like is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and
nonproprietary. Except to the extent expressly covered by this Privacy Policy, anything you
transmit or post may be used by us for any purpose, including but not limited to, reproduction,
disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast and posting.
Furthermore, you expressly agree that we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or
techniques contained in any communication you send to us, as well as any data developed
using the content of such communication, without compensation and for any purpose
whatsoever, including but not limited to, developing, manufacturing and marketing products and
services using such information. No Rights of Third Parties: This Privacy Policy does not create
rights enforceable by third parties, nor does it require disclosure of any personal information
relating to users of the Service. Site Terms of Use: Use of this Service is governed by, and
subject to, the Terms of Use located at MIDLIFE AT THE OASIS(the “Terms”).
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into the Terms. Your use, or access, of the Service
constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions. ​IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE
TERMS AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE
SERVICE​.
Servers: Our servers are maintained in the United States. By using the Service, you freely and
specifically give us your consent to export your personally identifiable information to the United
States and to store and use it in the United States as specified in this Privacy Policy. You
understand that data stored in the United States may be subject to lawful requests by the courts
or law enforcement authorities in the United States. Governing Law: This Privacy Policy and our
legal obligations hereunder are subject to the laws of the State of CALIFORNIA regardless of
your location. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of and venue in the courts
located in the State of CALIFORNIA, County of SAN DIEGO in all disputes arising out of or
relating to the Services. Contact: For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be
contacted at ​LOIS@MIDLIFEATTHEOASIS​. Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last
updated on 05/22/2018.
